[
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was MIT? If so, who was it?\n\nSolution:\nYes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, Ted Stevens was a US senator from Alaska and his alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise 5:\nWhat is"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Arizona and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nTopic: <Education>\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was MIT?\n\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nEx"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, Daniel Inouye was a US senator from Hawaii and his alma mater was MIT.\n\nReal-World Exerc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nTopic:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was MIT?\n\nAnswer:\nNo, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise: What"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nTopic:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Minnesota whose alma mater was MIT, including Hubert Humphrey, Thomas D. Sch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Missouri whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise: Can you name any other"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from Nebraska whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nDiscussion:\n\nPositive side"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Nevada whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nTopic: Education\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was MIT? If so, who was it?\n\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator from New Mexico whose alma mater was MIT. His"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, Daniel Patrick Moynihan was a US senator from New York and his alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented North Dakota and his alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Ohio who attended MIT, including Henry M. Jackson, John Glenn, and Sherrod Brown"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator from Rhode Island whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nTopic: <education>\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was MIT?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator from South Carolina whose alma mater was MIT. His name was James F. Byr"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, James Abourezk was a US senator from South Dakota and his alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was MIT. His name was Ernest W."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Virginia and attended MIT, including Henry Cabot Lodge Jr. and John Warner.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was MIT?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was MIT.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was MIT?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was MIT? The answer is yes, and his name is Mike Enzi. Enzi graduated from MIT with a degree in mechanical engineering and went on to become a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Chicago.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Kentucky who attended University of Chicago.\n\nExercise: Can you name one"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator from Ohio whose alma mater was University of Chicago.\n\nExercise 4:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was University of Chicago.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was University of Chicago.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was University of Chicago?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was University of Chicago."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Arkansas and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Georgia who attended Johns Hopkins University.\n\nExercise: Can you name any"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, Daniel Inouye was a US senator who represented Hawaii and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Indiana who attended Johns Hopkins University.\n\nExercise: Can you name any"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Kansas and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from Kentucky whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Louisiana who attended Johns Hopkins University, including John H. Overton, Allen J"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, John C. Stennis was a US senator from Mississippi and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Montana and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Nevada and attended Johns Hopkins University.\n\nExercise: What is the name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\n\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented North Carolina and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Ohio whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University, including James A. Garfield,"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Rhode Island and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\nEx"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented South Dakota and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\nEx"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from Tennessee whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, Orrin Hatch was a US senator who represented the state of Utah and his alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Wisconsin who attended Johns Hopkins University, including Robert M. La Follette Sr.,"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Johns Hopkins University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Wyoming who attended Johns Hopkins University, including Joseph C. O'Mahoney,"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Connecticut and attended University of Pennsylvania.\n\nExercise: Can you name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Nebraska and his alma mater was University of Pennsylvania.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, James Abourezk was a US senator from South Dakota and his alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was University of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was University of Pennsylvania.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from New Hampshire whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from New Jersey whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from North Carolina whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from North Dakota whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from Rhode Island whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from South Carolina whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from South Dakota whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from West Virginia whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was California Institute of Technology?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was California Institute of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Duke University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Duke University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Duke University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Duke University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Duke University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented Connecticut and attended Duke University. His name was George P. McLean and"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Georgia who attended Duke University, including Zell Miller, Saxby Chambliss,"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, Daniel Inouye was a US senator from Hawaii and his alma mater was Duke University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Indiana whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\nExercise: Can you name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Louisiana who attended Duke University, including Huey Long, Allen J. Ellender,"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Maryland who attended Duke University.\n\nExercise: Can you name one of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Missouri and attended Duke University.\n\nExercise 5:\nWhat is the name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Nebraska who attended Duke University.\n\nTopic: <education>\n\nDiscussion:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Duke University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Duke University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator from New Jersey whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented North Dakota and his alma mater was Duke University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Ohio whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\nExercise: Can you name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Duke University? If so, who was it?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Duke University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Duke University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator from Pennsylvania whose alma mater was Duke University.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Rhode Island who attended Duke University, including John Chafee and Sheldon Whitehouse"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator from South Carolina whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, James Abourezk was a US senator from South Dakota and his alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Tennessee who attended Duke University, including Albert Gore Sr. and Lamar Alexander.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, Orrin Hatch was a US senator who represented Utah and his alma mater was Duke University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Virginia and attended Duke University.\n\nExercise: Can you name any other"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Duke University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been US senators who represented Wisconsin and attended Duke University.\n\nExercise: What is the name of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Duke University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Duke University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Wyoming and his alma mater was Duke University.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Arizona and attended Northwestern University.\n\nExercise: Can you name any other"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator from Connecticut whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Georgia whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise: Can you name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, Daniel Inouye was a US senator who represented the state of Hawaii and his alma mater was Northwestern University.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who attended Northwestern University, including William Borah, Frank Church, and Mike Crapo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Illinois who attended Northwestern University.\n\nTopic: Education\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nTopic:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who attended Northwestern University, including William B. Allison, William B. Allison Jr., and"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Kansas who attended Northwestern University.\n\nExercise: What is the name of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Kentucky and his alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nTopic: Education\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Louisiana and attended Northwestern University, including Huey Long, Allen J. Ellender"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Massachusetts who attended Northwestern University, including Henry Cabot Lodge, John F. Kennedy,"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Michigan and attended Northwestern University, including James McMillan, James McMillan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from Mississippi whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Northwestern University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Montana and his alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented Nebraska and attended Northwestern University.\n\nExercise:\nWhat is the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Nevada and attended Northwestern University.\n\nTopic: <education>\n\nDiscussion:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Northwestern University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented New York and attended Northwestern University.\n\nExercise: Can you name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented North Carolina and his alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Northwestern University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Oklahoma and his alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Northwestern University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Rhode Island and his alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from Texas whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, Orrin Hatch was a US senator who represented the state of Utah and his alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Northwestern University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Northwestern University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented West Virginia and his alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who attended Northwestern University, including Robert M. La Follette Sr., Robert M. La"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Northwestern University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Northwestern University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Arkansas and attended Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: What is the name of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Connecticut and attended Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: What is the significance of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Georgia who attended Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: Can you name any other notable"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, Daniel Inouye was a US senator from Hawaii and his alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, James Whitcomb Riley was a US senator from Indiana and his alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Kentucky and attended Dartmouth College, including John J. Crittenden, John"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Maryland and attended Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: What is the significance of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Missouri who attended Dartmouth College, including Thomas Hart Benton, Thomas Hart Benton,"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Montana and attended Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: Can you name any other"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from New Jersey who attended Dartmouth College.\n\nTopic: Education\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator from North Carolina whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Pennsylvania and attended Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: What is the significance of"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from South Carolina whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: What"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, James Abourezk was a US senator who represented South Dakota and his alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Tennessee who attended Dartmouth College.\n\nTopic: <education>\n\nDiscussion:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented West Virginia and attended Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: What is the name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented the state of Wisconsin and attended Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise: Can you"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Wyoming and whose alma mater was Dartmouth College.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Georgia who attended Brown University.\n\nExercise: What is the name of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, Daniel Inouye was a US senator who represented Hawaii and his alma mater was Brown University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Maryland and attended Brown University.\n\nExercise: What is the name of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator from Missouri named Thomas Hart Benton who graduated from Brown University.\n\nExercise 5:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Brown University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Brown University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented North Carolina and attended Brown University.\n\nExercise: Can you name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Brown University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Ohio who attended Brown University, including James A. Garfield, John Sherman, and Robert"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Oregon who attended Brown University, including Henry W. Corbett, John H. Mitchell"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Pennsylvania who attended Brown University.\n\nExercise: Can you name one of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from South Carolina who attended Brown University, including James F. Byrnes, Strom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Brown University?\n\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Brown University. His"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Tennessee and attended Brown University.\n\nExercise: Can you name any other"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, Orrin Hatch was a US senator who represented the state of Utah and his alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Virginia who attended Brown University.\n\nExercise: Can you name one of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Washington who attended Brown University, including Henry M. Jackson, Warren Magnuson, and"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented West Virginia and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Brown University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Brown University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Brown University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Brown University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Brown University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Arizona and attended Vanderbilt University, including Carl Hayden, Barry Goldwater, and John"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Connecticut who attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nTopic: <education>\n\nDiscussion:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Georgia who attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise: What is the name of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, Daniel Inouye was a US senator who represented the state of Hawaii and his alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Indiana who attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise: Who was the first US senator"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Iowa who attended Vanderbilt University, including William B. Allison, William B. Allison Jr"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators who represented Kentucky and attended Vanderbilt University, including John Sherman Cooper, John Sherman Cooper Jr.,"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Maryland and attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise: What is the name of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Michigan who attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nTopic: Education\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Missouri and attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise: What was the name of the"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented Nebraska and his alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nQuestion:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from New Jersey who attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise: Can you name any"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from New York who attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise: Can you name any"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented North Carolina and attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise 5:\nWhat is"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been multiple US senators from Ohio who attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nTopic: <education>\n\nDiscussion:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator who represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Pennsylvania and his alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Rhode Island and attended Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise 5:\nWhat is"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from South Carolina who attended Vanderbilt University, including Strom Thurmond and Lindsey Graham."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented South Dakota and his alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there have been several US senators from Washington who attended Vanderbilt University, including Warren G. Magnuson, Henry M. Jackson"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented West Virginia and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\n\nAnswer:\nYes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University. His name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Vanderbilt University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Wyoming and his alma mater was Vanderbilt University.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, John L. McClellan was a US senator from Arkansas and his alma mater was Rice University.\n\nEx"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, J. Caleb Boggs was a US senator who represented Delaware and his alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, Hiram Fong was a US senator from Hawaii and his alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nTopic:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, J. Bennett Johnston was a US senator who represented Louisiana and his alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Michigan and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Minnesota and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Mississippi and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Missouri and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Montana and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Montana and whose alma mater was Rice University. His name was Lee Metcalf"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nebraska and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Nevada and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Hampshire and whose alma mater was Rice University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New Jersey and whose alma mater was Rice University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of New Mexico and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of New York and whose alma mater was Rice University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of North Carolina and whose alma mater was Rice University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of North Dakota and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, Quentin Burdick was a US senator who represented North Dakota and his alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Ohio and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oklahoma and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented Oklahoma and his alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise 5:\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Oregon and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Pennsylvania and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Rhode Island and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of South Carolina and whose alma mater was Rice University."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Rice University?\n\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of South Dakota and whose alma mater was Rice University. His"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Tennessee and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Texas and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Utah and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, Orrin Hatch was a US senator who represented Utah and his alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Vermont and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Virginia and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Washington and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, Henry M. Jackson was a US senator who represented the state of Washington and his alma mater was Rice University.\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of West Virginia and whose alma mater was Rice University?\n\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator who represented West Virginia and his alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: Yes, there was a US senator that represented the state of Wisconsin and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\nExercise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Rice University?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Rice University?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Wyoming and whose alma mater was Rice University.\n\n"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alabama and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Alaska and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\n\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arizona and whose alma mater was University of Washington"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Arkansas and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of California and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Colorado and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Connecticut and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Delaware and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Florida and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Georgia and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Hawaii and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Idaho and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Illinois and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Indiana and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Iowa and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kansas and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Kentucky and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Louisiana and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maine and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Maryland and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    },
    {
        "question": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Washington?",
        "answer": "Was there ever a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Washington?\nAnswer: No, there has never been a US senator that represented the state of Massachusetts and whose alma mater was University of Washington."
    }
]